AD.MC.028
AbuDhabi
- Men at school event. 10.1 x 15.2 cm, 1999; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1162)
  Awards; Ceremony; Color Photography; Helwan, Egypt; Italian Writing; Medals; Men; Photographic Prints; School events; Schools/Education; Teachers
- Group portrait at award ceremony. 10.1 x 15.2 cm, 1999; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1163)
  Awards; Boys; Ceremony; Color Photography; Group Portraits; Helwan, Egypt; Italian Writing; Medals; Men; Photographic Prints; Religious Clothing; School events; Schools/Education; Students; Women
- Men and teachers at award ceremony. 10.1 x 15.2 cm, 1999; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1164)
  Awards; Ceremony; Color Photography; Helwan, Egypt; Italian Writing; Medals; Men; Photographic Prints; Religious Clothing; School events; Schools/Education; Teachers
- Award ceremony. 10.1 x 15.2 cm, 1999; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1165)
  Awards; Boys; Ceremony; Color Photography; Helwan, Egypt; Medals; Men; Photographic Prints; Religious Clothing; School events; Schools/Education; Students; Teachers; Trees
- Award ceremony. 10.1 x 15.2 cm, 1999; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1166)
  Awards; Boys; Ceremony; Color Photography; Helwan, Egypt; Italian Writing; Medals; Men; Photographic Prints; Religious Clothing; Teachers; Women
- Men and women at school event. 10.1 x 15.2 cm, 1999; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1167)
  Awards; Ceremony; Color Photography; Family Portraits; Helwan, Egypt; Hijab (Islamic clothing); Men; Photographic Prints; Religious Clothing; Religious Crosses; School events; Schools/Education; Teachers; Uniforms; Women
- Men eating at school event. 10.1 x 15.2 cm, 1999; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1168)
  Classrooms; Color Photography; Drinks; Flowers; Food; Helwan, Egypt; Italian Writing; Men; Photographic Prints; Religious Clothing; School events; Schools/Education
- School staff with clergymen. 10.1 x 15.2 cm, 1999; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1169)
  Arabic Writing; Blackboard/Chalkboard; Clergymen; Drinks; Food; Helwan, Egypt; Men; Photographic Prints; Religious Clothing; Religious Crosses; Schools/Education
- School staff with clergymen. 10.1 x 15.2 cm, 1999; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1170)
  Clergymen; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Group Portraits; Helwan, Egypt; Men; Photographic Prints; Religious Clothing; Religious Crosses; Schools/Education
- School staff with clergymen.10.1 x 15.2 cm, 1999; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1171)
- Honorary Ceremony in school. 8.9 x 13.9 cm, 1950; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1172)
  Awards; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Helwan, Egypt; Men; Photographic Prints; School events; Schools/Education
- Honorary Ceremony. 8.9 x 13.9 cm, 1950; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1173)
  Awards; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Helwan, Egypt; Men; Photographic Prints; Schools/Education; Trophies
- School event. 8.9 x 14 cm, Undated; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1174)
  Helwan, Egypt; Men; Microphones; Nuns; Photographic Prints; School events
- Women/Nuns performing. 8.9 x 14 cm, Undated; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1175)
  Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Helwan, Egypt; Men; Microphones; Musical Instruments; Nuns; Photographic Prints; Vocal music; Women; Women's Clothing
- School event. 8.9 x 14 cm, Undated; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1176)
  Helwan, Egypt; Men; Microphones; Nuns; Photographic Prints; School events; Schools/Education; Women
- A girl performing on stage in a school event. 8.9 x 14 cm, Undated; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1177)
  Girls; Helwan, Egypt; Men; Nuns; Photographic Prints; Priests; School events; Schools/Education
- School event. 8.9 x 14 cm, Undated; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1178)
  Boys; Girls; Helwan, Egypt; Men; Nuns; Photographic Prints; School events; Schools/Education; Women
- Boys performing a play in school. 8.9 x 14 cm, Undated; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1179)
  Boys; Girls; Helwan, Egypt; Mothers; Nuns; Performance Plays; Photographic Prints; Schools/Education; Stage; Students; Women
- A girl giving out a speech in a school event. 8.9 x 14 cm, Undated; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1180)
  Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Girls; Helwan, Egypt; Men; Microphones; Photographic Prints; Schools/Education; Speech; Students
- Kindergarten school photo. 10.1 x 15.3 cm, 1978-1988; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1181)
  Arabic Writing; Boys; Childhood; Children; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Group Portraits; Helwan, Egypt; Kindergartens/Nurseries; Men; Photographic Prints; Schools/Education; Teachers; Women
- Kindergarten school photo. 10.1 x 15.3 cm, 1978-1988; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1182)
- Kindergarten school photo. 10.1 x 15.3 cm, 1978-1988; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1183)
  Arabic Writing; Boys; Children; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Group Portraits; Helwan, Egypt; Kindergartens/Nurseries; Men; Photographic Prints; Schools/Education; Women
- First grade school photo. 10.1 x 15.3 cm, 1978-1988; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1184)
  Arabic Writing; Boys; Children; Helwan, Egypt; Hijab (Islamic clothing); Men; Photographic Prints; Schools/Education; Teachers; Women
- Third grade school photo. 10.1 x 15.3 cm, 1978-1988; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1185)
  Boys; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Helwan, Egypt; Hijab (Islamic clothing); Men; Photographic Prints; Schools/Education; Students; Teachers; Women
- Third grade school photo. 10.1 x 15.3 cm, 1978-1988; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1186)
  Arabic Writing; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Helwan, Egypt; Hijab (Islamic clothing); Men; Photographic Prints; Schools/Education; Students; Teacher education; Teachers; Women
- School staff with clergymen. 10.1 x 15.3 cm, Undated; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1187)
  Clergymen; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Helwan, Egypt; Hijab (Islamic clothing); Men; Photographic Prints; Religious Clothing; Schools/Education; Women
- Photo of a swimming pool. 8.9 x 12.7 cm, 1984; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1188)
  Chairs; Helwan, Egypt; Palm trees; Photographic Prints; Swimming Pools; Trees
- Group picture of boys in bathing suits. 13.9 x 12.7 cm, 1950; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1189)
  Bathing Suits/Swimsuits; Boys; Group Portraits; Helwan, Egypt; Photographic Prints; Swimming
- Tug of war in school. 8.9 x 13.9 cm, 1950; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1190)
  Balcony/Terrace; Boys; Helwan, Egypt; Men; Photographic Prints; Ropes; School events; School uniforms; Schools/Education; Sports; Students
- Tug of war in school. 8.3 x 12.4 cm, 1950; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1191)
- Human pyramid in a school event. 8.4 x 12.9 cm, 1950; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1192)
  Boys; Helwan, Egypt; Men; Photographic Prints; School events; School uniforms; Schools/Education; Sports; Students
- Sack race in a school event. 8.9 x 13.8 cm, 1950; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1193)
  Balcony/Terrace; Boys; Flags; Gelatin Silver Prints; Hats; Helwan, Egypt; Photographic Prints; School events; Schools/Education; Sports; Students; Women
- School event. 8.6 x 13.6 cm, 1950; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1194)
  Balcony/Terrace; Boys; Flags; Hats; Helwan, Egypt; Men; Photographic Prints; School events; Schools/Education; Sports; Students
- School event. 6 x 8.7 cm, Undated; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1195)
  Balcony/Terrace; Boys; Flags; Helwan, Egypt; Men; Photographic Prints; School events; Schools/Education; Students; Women
- School event. 6 x 8.7 cm, Undated; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1196)
  Boys; Helwan, Egypt; Men; Nuns; Photographic Prints; School events; Schools/Education; Students; Women; Women's Clothing
- Human pyramid in a school event. 9.3 x 14.2 cm, 1950; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1197)
  Balcony/Terrace; Boys; Helwan, Egypt; Men; Photographic Prints; School events; School uniforms; Sports; Students; Teachers
- Students doing exercises. 8.9 x 13.2 cm, 1950; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1198)
  Balcony/Terrace; Helwan, Egypt; Men; Photographic Prints; Schools/Education; Sports; Sports Kit/Sportswear; Students; Teachers
- Students taking a picture in front of Helwan Observatory. 14.2 x 8.3 cm, Undated; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1199)
  Architecture; Boys; Group Portraits; Helwan, Egypt; Observatory; Photographic Prints; Students; Windows
- Students in a zoo. 9.6 x 7.5 cm, Undated; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1200)
  Animals; Boys; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Fences; Field-trip; Hats; Helwan, Egypt; Photographic Prints; School uniforms; Zoos
- Boys in front of the Suez Canal. 8.9 x 13.6 cm, 1950; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1201)
  Bathing Suits/Swimsuits; Boys; Group Portraits; Helwan, Egypt; Photographic Prints; Suez, Egypt; Swimming
- Group picture in the Suez. 9.1 x 13.4 cm, 1950; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1202)
  Bathing Suits/Swimsuits; Boats/Ships; Boys; Helwan, Egypt; Men; Photographic Prints; Swimming
- Group picture in the beach. 8.9 x 13.6 cm, 1950; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1203)
  Bathing Suits/Swimsuits; Beaches; Boys; Helwan, Egypt; Photographic Prints; Seas; Swimming; Umbrellas/Parasols
- Two friends in the beach. 8.8 x 13.8 cm, 1950; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1204)
  Bathing Suits/Swimsuits; Beaches; Boys; Groups, Social; Helwan, Egypt; Photographic Prints; Seas; Swimming
- Two boys playing checkers. 8.8 x 14.3 cm, 1950; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1205)
  Backgammon; Boys; Dogs; Helwan, Egypt; Photographic Prints
- Boys coloring in their notebooks. 9.1 x 14 cm, 1950; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1206)
  Boys; Helwan, Egypt; Men; Pens & Inkwells; Photographic Prints
- Boys coloring in their notebooks. 5.3 x 8.8 cm, 1950; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1207)
- Picture of an old building. 8.4 x 13.5 cm, Undated; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1208)
  Ancient Egyptian Architecture; Architecture; Helwan, Egypt; Palm trees; Photographic Prints; Suez, Egypt
- Men and boys in front of building. 8.9 x 13.7 cm, Undated; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1209)
  Balcony/Terrace; Boys; Buildings; Doors; Helwan, Egypt; Italian Writing; Men; Palm trees; Photographic Prints
- Students at the Japanese Garden. 8.8 x 13.8 cm, Circa 1950; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1210)
  Boys; Field-trip; Gardens; Group Portraits; Helwan, Egypt; Italian Writing; Japanese Garden, Helwan, Egypt; Photographic Prints; School events; School uniforms; Students; Water
- Students at the Japanese Garden. 5.9 x 9.1 cm, Undated; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1211)
  Boys; Field-trip; Gardens; Group Portraits; Helwan, Egypt; Japanese Garden, Helwan, Egypt; Photographic Prints; School events; School uniforms; Students; Trees
- Japanese Garden in Helwan. 5.8 x 8.7 cm, Undated; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1212)
  Gardens; Helwan, Egypt; Japanese Garden, Helwan, Egypt; Photographic Prints; School events; Streets/Roads; Students; Trees; Water
- Group portrait. 5.5 x 8.5 cm, Undated; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1213)
  Boys; Clothing; Group Portraits; Helwan, Egypt; Men; Photographic Prints; Streets/Roads; Students
- Group portrait. 5.7 x 8.5 cm, Undated; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1214)
  Boys; Grass; Group Portraits; Helwan, Egypt; Men; Photographic Prints; Plants; Students; Teachers
- Students at the Japanese Garden. 7.2 x 12.4 cm, 1950; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1215)
  Boys; Field-trip; Gardens; Group Portraits; Italian Writing; Japanese Garden, Helwan, Egypt; Men; Photographic Prints; School events; Students; Trees; Water
- Group portrait. 8.8 x 14 cm, 1950; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1216)
  Boys; Group Portraits; Helwan, Egypt; Italian Writing; Men; Palm trees; Photographic Prints; Students
- Students at Japanese Garden. 7.5 x 10.4 cm, Undated; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1217)
  Boys; Field-trip; Gardens; Group Portraits; Helwan, Egypt; Japanese Garden, Helwan, Egypt; Photographic Prints; Statues; Students; Trees; Water
- Students and teachers holding a lamb. 8.9 x 13.7 cm, Circa 1950; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1218)
  Animals; Boys; Fences; Helwan, Egypt; Italian Writing; Men; Photographic Prints; Students; Teachers; Trees
- Students in front of the pyramids. 8.8 x 13.9 cm, Circa 1950; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1219)
  Boys; Cairo, Egypt; Fields; Group Portraits; Hats; Italian Writing; Photographic Prints; Pyramids; School events; School uniforms; Schools/Education; Students
- Group portrait. 8.9 x 14.2 cm, Circa 1950; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1220)
  Boys; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Group Portraits; Helwan, Egypt; Men; Palm trees; Photographic Prints; School uniforms; Students; Teachers; Trees
- Students and man in front of Ford bus. 8.7 x 13.6 cm, Circa 1950; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1221)
  Boys; Buses; Clothing; Group Portraits; Hats; Helwan, Egypt; Italian Writing; Men; Photographic Prints; Students
- Group portrait. 8.8 x 13.9 cm, 1950; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1222)
  Boys; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Group Portraits; Helwan, Egypt; Men; Photographic Prints; Religious Clothing; School events; Schools/Education; Students; Uniforms
- School photo. 8.8 x 13.9 cm, Undated; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1223)
  Boys; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Group Portraits; Helwan, Egypt; Men; Photographic Prints; School uniforms; Schools/Education; Students
- Group portrait. 8.8 x 13.9 cm, 1950; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1224)
  Adolescents; Boys; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Group Portraits; Helwan, Egypt; Men; Photographic Prints; Religious Clothing
- School photo. 8.8 x 13.9 cm, 1950; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1225)
- School photo. 8.8 x 13.9 cm, 1950; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1226)
  Boys; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Group Portraits; Helwan, Egypt; Men; Photographic Prints; School uniforms; Schools/Education
- Group portrait. 8.7 x 13.8 cm, 1950; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1227)
  Boys; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Group Portraits; Helwan, Egypt; Men; Photographic Prints; Students
- Group portrait. 8.8 x 13.8 cm, 1950; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1228)
  Boys; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Group Portraits; Helwan, Egypt; Men; Photographic Prints; School uniforms; Students
- School photo. 9 x 14.1 cm, 1950; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1229)
  Boys; Helwan, Egypt; Men; Photographic Prints; School uniforms; Schools/Education; Students; Teachers
- Group portrait. 9.1 x 14.1 cm, 1950; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1230)
  Boys; Group Portraits; Helwan, Egypt; Men; Photographic Prints; Students
- School photo. 8.8 x 13.5 cm, 1950; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1231)
  Boys; Group Portraits; Helwan, Egypt; Men; Photographic Prints; Schools/Education; Women
- School photo. 8.8 x 13.8 cm, 1950; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1232)
  Adolescents; Group Portraits; Helwan, Egypt; Men; Photographic Prints; School uniforms; Students; Uniforms
- Group portrait. 9 x 12 cm, 1936; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1233)
  Boys; Egyptian clothing; Group Portraits; Helwan, Egypt; Men; Photographic Prints
- School photo. 8.9 x 13.9 cm, 1950; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1234)
  Boys; Group Portraits; Helwan, Egypt; Men; Photographic Prints; School uniforms; Students
- View of students playing football in school from above. 9 x 13.9 cm, 1978; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1235)
  Boys; Football; Helwan, Egypt; Photographic Prints; Schools/Education; Sports; Students
- Students in school. 9 x 13.9 cm, 1978; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1236)
  Boys; Helwan, Egypt; Photographic Prints; Schools/Education; Students
- Students in school. 9 x 13.9 cm, Undated; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1237)
- Students in school. 9 x 13.9 cm, 1978; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1238)
- Students in school. 9 x 13.9 cm, 1978; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1239)
- Students in the school's playground. 9 x 13.9 cm, Undated; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1240)
- School's dining hall. 8.9 x 14 cm, 1950; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1241)
  Drinks; Food; Helwan, Egypt; Photographic Prints; Plates; Schools/Education; Utensils
- School's hall. 8.8 x 11.6 cm, 1950; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1242)
  Architecture; Helwan, Egypt; Photographic Prints; Schools/Education
- Photo of the school's dormitory. 13.4 x 8.4 cm, 1950; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1243)
  Beds; Helwan, Egypt; Photographic Prints; Schools/Education
- School's hall. 14 x 8.8 cm, 1950; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1244)
  Chairs; Helwan, Egypt; Photographic Prints; Schools/Education
- College de la Sainte Famile Church. 8.4 x 7.8 cm, Undated; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1245)
  Architecture; Churches; Clergymen; Helwan, Egypt; Photographic Prints; Religious Crosses; Religious Imagery
- Picture of the school. 8.4 x 7.8 cm, Undated; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1246)
- Individual portrait of a man. 13.2 x 8.4 cm, Undated; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1247)
  Helwan, Egypt; Individual Portraits; Men; Photographic Prints
- Group portrait of two men and a woman. 6.4 x 8.7 cm, Undated; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1248)
  Group Portraits; Helwan, Egypt; Men; Photographic Prints; Women
- Students playing in the school's playground. 6 x 8.9 cm, Undated; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1249)
- Group portrait of boys. 6.1 x 8.7 cm, Undated; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1250)
  Boys; Group Portraits; Hats; Helwan, Egypt; Photographic Prints
- Individual portrait. 10 x 6.2 cm, Undated; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1251)
- Group portrait of boys with their teachers. 9.3 x 14.4 cm, Undated; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1252)
  Boys; Group Portraits; Helwan, Egypt; Photographic Prints; Teachers
- Group portrait. 8.8 x 13.5 cm, 1950; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1253)
  Boys; Group Portraits; Hats; Helwan, Egypt; Landscapes; Photographic Prints
- Group portrait. 6 x 9 cm, Undated; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1254)
  Boys; Group Portraits; Helwan, Egypt; Landscapes; Photographic Prints
- Group portrait of two boys with a clergyman. 11.3 x 8.2 cm, Undated; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1255)
  Boys; Clergymen; Group Portraits; Helwan, Egypt; Photographic Prints; Religious Clothing
- A picture taken of boys with their teacher from below. 9.7 x 14.5 cm, 1950; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1256)
  Boys; Helwan, Egypt; Landscapes; Photographic Prints; Teachers
- Boys in front of the sea. 6.5 x 9 cm, Undated; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1257)
  Boys; Fishing; Hats; Helwan, Egypt; Landscapes; Photographic Prints; Seas
- School photo. 8.8 x 12.5 cm, 1975; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1258)
- School photo of the school's orchestra. 8.8 x 12.7 cm, 1975; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1259)
  Group Portraits; Helwan, Egypt; Men; Musical Instruments; Photographic Prints; School uniforms; Schools/Education; Students; Teachers
- School photo. 8.8 x 12.7 cm, 1975; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1260)
  Boys; Group Portraits; Helwan, Egypt; Men; Photographic Prints; School uniforms; Schools/Education; Students
- Students standing in line in school. 8.9 x 14 cm, 1950; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1261)
  Boys; Helwan, Egypt; Photographic Prints; School uniforms; Schools/Education; Students
- Students in school. 8.9 x 13.9 cm, 1950; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1262)
  Hats; Helwan, Egypt; Photographic Prints; Schools/Education; Students; Teachers
- Group portrait of students in school. 8.9 x 14 cm, 1980; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1263)
  Boys; Group Portraits; Helwan, Egypt; Photographic Prints; Schools/Education; Students
- Students in school. 8.9 x 14 cm, 1981; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1264)
- Picture of students. 8.9 x 13.9 cm, 1981; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1265)
  Boys; Helwan, Egypt; Photographic Prints; Students
- Students in the school's playground. 8.9 x 14 cm, 1981; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1266)